hi everyone I'm talking to you today
from Melbourne Australia where it's
sunny and warm much unlike Toronto I
left there five days ago and it was
blizzardy and cold so it's really nice
to see the Sun I've been here with my
wife Tammy and a good crew Dane he is
the name of the crew that I'm travelling
with a production company and they've
been really good we've been to Perth did
two shows there to Adelaide have a show
tonight at Melbourne with about 5,000
people then Canberra Sydney Brisbane
Auckland Christchurch Wellington
Auckland again Sydney Melbourne and
Brisbane I just wanted to let you know
that there are tickets left to a number
of the shows on Thursday February 21st
at the Michael Fowler Centre in
Wellington New Zealand Theroux tickets
available on Saturday February 23rd at
the Logan Campbell Centre in Auckland
New Zealand there are tickets available
Tuesday February 26th at the ICC Sydney
Theatre at darling harbour on Wednesday
February 27th at the plenary Melbourne
Convention and Exhibition Centre in
Melbourne as you might have expected
there are also tickets available and
then finally Thursday February 28th at
the Brisbane Convention and Exhibition
Centre they can all be found at Jordan B
Peterson dot-com forward slash events
and so many of these shows are selling
out at a relatively rapid rate these
latter ones were ones we added because
there was additional popular demand so
if you do want to see that 12 rules for
life lectures this would be a good
opportunity to do it thanks to everyone
in Australia and New Zealand so far for
making this a very productive and
positive trip I hope to see you there
the shows have been very gratifying and
useful and productive and meaningful and
positive all of those things there are
serious conversations everyone seems to
be
I would say engaged by them and focused
and it's altogether a positive thing so
if you're interested the tickets are
available and I'll put a little bit more
information down at the bottom of the
screen on the description of the video
so I hope to see you there
thanks very much for all the support
it's much appreciated and quite the
remarkable experience I would say bye
bye